securenetsystems.net 2019-05-16

# Securenet Systems’ Online Privacy Policy

**This Privacy Statement is effective as of May 2018.**

Securenet Systems recognizes the importance of protecting your personal information and is committed to processing and storing it responsibly and in compliance with applicable data protection laws.

This Privacy Statement describes Securenet Systems' general privacy practices that apply to personal information we collect, use and share about consumers and other individuals within our clients, business partners, supplier and other organizations with which Securenet Systems has or contemplates a business relationship.

**Why and how we collect and use your personal information**

We may collect your personal information as an individual for various purposes, such as the following:

  1. **Access and use of websites or other online services**

When entering one of our websites, or using an online service, we will record information necessary to provide you with access, for the operation of the website and for us to comply with security and legal requirements in relation to operating our site, such as passwords, IP address and browser settings. We also collect information about your activities during your visit in order to personalize your website experience, such as recording your preferences and settings, and to collect statistics to help us improve and further develop our websites, products and services.

  2. **Responding to your request for information, order, or support**

When you contact us (online or offline) in connection with a request for information, to order a product or service, to provide you with support, we collect information necessary to fulfill your request, to grant you access to the product or service, to provide you with support and to be able to contact you. For instance, we collect your name and contact information, details about your request and your agreement with us and the fulfillment, delivery and invoicing of your order and we may include client satisfaction survey information. We retain such information for administrative purposes, defending our rights, and in connection with our relationship with you.

When you provide your name and contact information to register in connection with such a request, the registration may serve to identify you when you visit our websites. For ordering of services we require you to have registered as a Securenet Systems customer with an online user ID.

  3. **Contacting employees of our clients, prospects, partners and suppliers**

In our relationship with clients or prospects, partners and suppliers, they also provide us with business contact information (such as name, business contact details, position or title of their employees, contractors, advisors and authorized users) for purposes such as contract management, fulfillment, delivery of services, provision of support, invoicing and management of the services or the relationship.

  4. **Marketing**

Most information we collect about you comes from our direct interactions with you. You can choose to receive information by email or telephone about our services, or sign-up for subscriptions. When visiting our websites or using our services we may provide you with personalized information. You can always opt-out from receiving personalized communication by sending an e-mail to [info@securenetsystems.net](mailto:info@securenetsystems.net).

Where we reference that we use your personal information in connection with a request, order, transaction or agreement (or preparing for the same), or to provide you with services that you requested (such as a streaming player), we do this because it is necessary for the performance of an agreement with you.

Where we reference that we use your personal information in relation to marketing, improvement or development of our products or services, for reasons of safety and security, or regulatory requirements other than in connection with your agreement or request, we do this on the basis of our or a third party's legitimate interests, or with your consent. When we collect and use your personal information subject to the EU Privacy Legislation please also refer to the "Your Rights" section below.

**Sharing of personal information**

Securenet Systems generally does not share any information about you except when needed due to business practices, such as processing payments with third-party banking institutions, or where required by law.

If Securenet Systems decides to sell, buy, or merge businesses, such a transaction may involve the disclosure of personal information to prospective or actual purchasers, or the receipt of such information from sellers. It is Securenet Systems' practice to require appropriate protection for personal information in these types of transactions.

Please be aware that in certain circumstances, personal information may be subject to disclosure to government agencies pursuant to judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process. We may also share your personal information to protect the rights or property of Securenet Systems, our business partners, suppliers or clients, and others when we have reasonable grounds to believe that such rights or property have been or could be affected.

**Storage of personal information**

All personal information is stored in the United States of America.

**Information security and accuracy**

We intend to protect your personal information and to maintain its accuracy. Securenet Systems implements reasonable physical, administrative and technical safeguards to help us protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use and disclosure. For example, we encrypt certain sensitive personal information such as credit card information when we transmit such information over the Internet. We also require that our suppliers protect such information from unauthorized access, use and disclosure.

**Retention period**

We will not retain personal information longer than necessary to fulfill the purposes for which it is processed, including the security of our processing complying with legal and regulatory obligations (e.g. audit, accounting and statutory retention terms), handling disputes, and for the establishment, exercise or defense of legal claims in the countries where we do business.

**How to contact us**

If you have a question related to this Privacy Statement, please contact us by using the information below. Your message will be forwarded to the appropriate member of Securenet Systems' Data Privacy Team, such as Data Protection Officers or members of their teams.

For the purposes of the EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), the controller of your personal information is Securenet Systems, 356 SW 12th Ave, Deerfield Beach, Florida, United States of America.

**Your rights**

You can request to access, update or correct your personal information. You also have the right to object to direct marketing. You can contact us with your request as indicated below.

You may have additional rights pursuant to your local law applicable to the processing. For example, if the processing of your personal information is subject to the EU General Data Protection Regulation ("GDPR"), and your personal information is processed based on legitimate interests, you have the right to object to the processing on grounds relating to your specific situation. Under GDPR you may also have the right to request to have your personal information deleted or restricted and ask for portability of your personal information.

**Right to lodge a complaint**

In the event you consider our processing of your personal information not to be compliant with the applicable data protection laws, you can lodge a complaint:

Directly with Securenet Systems using the contact information below.

With the competent data protection authority. The name and contact details of the Data Protection Authorities in the European Union can be found at the URL below  
<http://ec.europa.eu/justice/article-29/structure/data-protection-authorities/index_en.htm>

**Contact information**

Please direct questions regarding this Statement or Securenet Systems' handling of your information to:

Securenet Systems  
Data Protection Officer  
356 SW 12th Ave  
Deerfield Beach, FL 33442  
U.S.A. 

If you do not want to receive future marketing communications from Securenet Systems, please send an email to [info@securenetsystems.net](mailto:info@securenetsystems.net)
